<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>says jerad</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on says jerad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>be a part of the lives that you care about</title>
      <link>/soup/participate-in-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/soup/participate-in-love/</guid>
      <description>Show them how much you care There is no sentiment analysis or crib notes for your inner-narrative. How ever lovely your thoughts and sentiment are of a person, they remain entirely yours. Sure, you can share your feelings. Concede this affection over a bottle of wine. The next day and thereafter, just like the wine, they may remember your words but they will not be sitting back enjoying their fruit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federalize the Fed to feed the economy</title>
      <link>/cool-talk/federal-fed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cool-talk/federal-fed/</guid>
      <description>What if the Fed printed money and distributed it through stimulus packages to citzens.. Fed currently prints money and to inject it into the economy it provides cheap loans. This money reaches the people by lowering mortgage rates. The money reaches companies similarly through reduced loan rates.
instead money could reach citzens directly and reach companies via consumer spending and investments that would theoretically be increased from the printed stimulus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The subconscious concequence of intimidation</title>
      <link>/belly-button/subconscious-intimidation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/belly-button/subconscious-intimidation/</guid>
      <description>We are not incentivizing the right parts of the mind Punishment deters the conscious mind; yet misbehavior abounds.
Our biggest example exists in our penitentiary system. Far from an applaudable rehabilitation system, the threat of prison is enough to keep our conscious mind from a primative life of lie, cheat, steal in the advancement of self.
The system is broken An overcrowded system and high incarceration rates indicate we revist the incentives schemes; rather than increasing perhaps we should redirect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why do I create music?</title>
      <link>/who-me/why-create/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/who-me/why-create/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the unessential The unnecessary has an interesting place in our lives. Surely we are gluttunous creatures with plenty of excess. Among the hoggish slop of redundance and the encumbering wealth of consumerism is a very specific form of unessential I am calling out here.
A very refined excess that is cultured by nature; culture, in-fact, is so bound with it, it is defined by and along-with this most uneeded of creations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>